[{
	"question": "What is the name of captian america?",
	"options": ["A.  Steve Rogers", 
		"B. Tony Steve", 
		"C. Bruce Banner", 
		"D. Tony Stark"],
	"answer": "A. Steve Rogers "
},
{
	"question": "Who was the first Avenger?",
	"options": ["A.Iron Man", 
		"B. Hawkeye", 
		"C. Captain America", 
		"D. Hulk"],
	"answer": "C. Captain America"
},
{
	"question": "What is the metal used in sheild of Captain America?",
	"options": ["A.Vibranium", 
		"B. Steel", 
		"C. Copper", 
		"D. Gold"],
	"answer": "A. Vibranium"
},
{
	"question": "Is Captain America a Human?",
	"options": ["A. True", 
		"B. False"], 
	"answer": "A. True"
},
{
	"question": "What is the stone used in Ultron?",
	"options": ["A. Soul stone", 
		"B. Mind Stone", 
		"C. time stone", 
		"D. Power stone"],
	"answer": "B. Mind Stone"
},
{
	"question": "Who created Ultron?",
	"options": ["A. Captain America", 
		"B. Iron-man", 
		"C. Both a&b", 
		"D. Hulk"],
	"answer": "B. Iron-man"
},
{
	"question": "Who was Ultron Girldfriend?",
	"options": ["A.Black-widow", 
		"B. Wanda Maximoff", 
		"C.Captain Marvel", 
		"D. None of the above"],
	"answer": "B. Wanda Maximoff"
},
{
	"question": "Who killed Ultron?",
	"options": ["A.Thanos", 
		"B. Loki", 
		"C. Hulk", 
		"D. Winter Soldier"],
	"answer": "A. Thanos"
},
{
	"question": "Who is Thor?",
	"options": ["A. God ", 
		"B.Human", 
		"C. Alien", 
		"D. None of the above"],
	"answer": "A.God"
},
{
	"question": "Who is Thor brother",
	"options": ["A.Iron Man", 
		"B. Hulk", 
		"C. Hawkeye", 
		"D. Loki"],
	"answer": "D. Loki"
},
{
	
	"question": "What is Thor Hammer-Name",
	"options": ["A.Lightstrom", 
		"B. friday", 
		"C. Mjollnir", 
		"D. shield"],
	"answer": "C. Mjollnir"
},
{
	"question": "What is Iron Man real name?",
	"options": ["A.Thor", 
		"B. Steve Rogures", 
		"C. Bruce Banner", 
		"D.Tony Stark"],
	"answer": "D. Tony Stark"
},
{
	"question": "What is tony stark AI name?",
	"options": ["A.Jarvis", 
		"B. Friday", 
		"C. strom", 
		"D. thnder"],
	"answer": "A. Jarvis"
},
{
	"question": "Is Iron Man Human?",
	"options": ["A.False", 
		"B. True"],
	"answer": "B. True"
},
{
	"question": "What is Thor power?",
	"options": ["A.Lightstrom", 
		"B. Lightning", 
		"C. strom", 
		"D. water"],
	"answer": "B. lightning"
},
{
	"question": "?",
	"options": ["A.Lightstrom", 
		"B. Lightning", 
		"C. strom", 
		"D. water"],
	"answer": "B. lightning"
}




]
